<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<rss version="2.0">

	<posta>
		<title>Lèon the Professional</title>
		<category>Action</category>
		<description>Lèon is one of the world's greatest assassins. A professional hitman, he lives a very discrete life and goes by a strict code: no women, no children. Lèon is extremely cautious and meticulous. He sleeps sitting upright in a chair with his gun to his side. You won't catch him making mistakes. Jean Reno plays Lèon, the professional. You soon realize he has a soft spot for Mathilda, a young girl played by Natalie Portman. Prior to this movie, I'd never heard of the actress, and to this day, I would say this was her finest acting to date. She plays a very influential part, and you can't help but feel bad for her after her parents are killed by the DEA (Drug Enforcement Agency). The antagonist is Stansfield (Gary Oldman), a crooked cop that has a heavy pill-popping addiction. Out of all the movies I've seen with "professional killers," Lèon The Professional stands out as one of the best, if not the greatest of all time. Others can claim to be the original hitman, but this one sets the bar. This movie can absolutely be accredited to building both Natalie Portman's and Gary Oldman's acting careers. Not only does it tell a great story, but it also has a wonderful ending that leaves you sad, happy, and satisfied all at once.</description>
		<pubDate>August 16, 2012</pubDate>
	</posta>
	
	<postb>
		<title>Ip Man</title>
		<category>Drama</category>
		<description>Yip Man is the first martial arts master to teach Wing Chun. He is reknowned as one of the greatest fighters of all time, so great, in fact, that he was the mentor and trainer for Bruce Lee. In the 1930s and '40s, he lived in Foshan, a humble city in southern China where martial arts schools flood the streets. Ip Man is the grand champion among them all, but he was not focused on instructing others. He wanted to live a simple life, and he did, until the Japanese invasion turned his home into their local headquarters. Even if you don't have any interest at all in Chinese culture or martial arts, this is an amazing must-see film to understand the beauty of humbleness in humanity. I, myself, am not the type to watch a movie like this. Infact, this is probably a movie many people would skip at first glance, however time and time again this movie has kept me thoroughly entertained. This is arguably one of the best martial-arts movies of all time. The martial arts sequences are precise and carefully directed. The environment is engulfing and you can really feel the poverty which affects everyone as war encroaches on their doorsteps. As a personal favorite, this movie will not disappoint, and is by far worth the two hour investment.</description>
		<pubDate>August 15, 2012</pubDate>
	</postb>
	
	<postc>
		<title>Riding in Cars with Boys</title>
		<category>Drama</category>
		<description>Riding in Cars with Boys is an older film, however it's definitely one of my all-time favorites. This movie is inspiring at the very least. Based on a true story, Drew Barrymore plays a single-mother with hopes of one day becoming a writer. During her journey, she manages a child, a failed marriage with the drug addicted father, and the pain of losing the only support system she has. This biography grasps reality in ways that other films cannot. It reminds us of the choices we take in life and how quickly things can go bad. However, you also have the warm feeling of success and closure as she finally achieves her goal.</description>
		<pubDate>August 14, 2012</pubDate>
	</postc>
	
	<postd>
		<title>The Prestige</title>
		<category>Drama</category>
		<description>I think we all have a part of us that is intrigued by magic. The Prestige is the story of a friendship that turns to rivalry between two magicians, Robert Angier (Hugh Jackman) and Alfred Borden (Christian Bale) and their quest to out-perform one another. This is a powerful movie inspired by innovation and illusion. Things really take a twist when Julia McCullough (Scarlet Johansson) accidentally dies during one of their performances. Robert blames Alfred for the incident and the hatred slowly builds between them. There are plenty of movies you can watch and can already foresee what will happen next. During The Prestige, you're always kept guessing or wondering if their next trick will be their last. Seeing how far they will go and what desparate mesures they will take to be the best is gratifying and exciting. The movie holds true to mystery and magic and inevitably pushes the boundaries of what is possible. Michael Caine plays Cutter, and is fantastic as usual. If you have watched any of the new Dark Knight series by Christopher Nolan, you can appreciate the relationship and chemistry between Michael Caine and Christian Bale. You will absolutely love this movie.</description>
		<pubDate>August 13, 2012</pubDate>
	</postd>
	
</rss>